What are they hiding?
Under the Silver Lake is a crime, drama, mystery film
directed by David Robert Mitchell.
Young and disenchanted Sam meets a mysterious and beautiful woman
who's swimming in his building's pool one night.
When she suddenly vanishes the next morning, Sam embarks on a surreal quest across Los Angeles to decode the secret
behind her disappearance, leading him into the murkiest depths of mystery, scandal and conspiracy.
Sam, played by Andrew Garfield.
Sarah, played by Riley Keough.
Bar Buddy, played by Topher Grace.
Millicent Sevence, played by Callie Hernandez.
Final Man, played by Don McManus.
Songwriter, played by Jeremy Bobb.
Under the Silver Lake is a 2018 American surrealist neo-noir black comedy
thriller film written, produced and directed by David Robert Mitchell.
Set in 2011 Los Angeles, it follows a young man (Andrew Garfield) investigating the sudden disappearance
of his neighbor (Riley Keough), only to stumble upon an elusive and dangerous conspiracy.
Under the Silver Lake premiered on May 15, 2018, at the Cannes Film Festival, where it
competed for the Palme d'Or, before being released nationwide in France on August 8.
It was released theatrically in the United States on April 19, 2019, by A24.
The film received polarized reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of secret society, seduction,
dark comedy, surrealism, dream sequence.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.